

YAHYA MOHAMMED

SOFTWARE **DEVELOPER**

CONTACT

+9647707939264

yahya_37m@proton.me

Iraq, Kirkuk

07-9-2000

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Python C++

[JavaScript]

Kotlin

Dart

Java C#

MySql

Sqlite

[Flutter] Flask

Android Studio

VannillaJS C

WSL

HTML

SFML Jinja

CSS3

Figma

Office Word Office Excel

CMake

SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership
- Public Speaking
- · Problem Solving
- Team Work
- Positivity

LANGUAGES

Arabic Native/Bilingual

Turkman Native/Bilingual

English Full Professional

Spanish **Limited Working**

Turkey **Professional Working**

SOCIAL

yahya-mohammed07

ABOUT ME

As a self-motivated Software Developer with over two years of experiencein C++, I have been involved in several open-source projects for writing, testing, and deploying. I have managed to be involved in the design, planning, development, testing, and production start-up of multiple projects. My proficiency in popular coding languages including Python, JavaScript, and C++ and frameworks or systems such as Flask and Git, along with my excellent knowledge of the software development life cycle, makes me a strong candidate for software developer positions. I have strong problem-solving and communication skills, knowledge of Object- Relational Mapping frameworks, and experience with Agile and Scrum development methodologies. I am able to learn quickly and work independently or as part of a team.

EXPERIENCE

LEAD DEVELOPER IN COLLEGE GRADUATION PROJECT

| Nov 2022 - May 2023

OPEN SOURCE DEVELOPER

| Mar 2020 - Current

Active contributor in Open-Source Projects.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF KIRKUK - COMPUTER SCIENCE DEPT.

Iraq, Kirkuk | Nov 2019 - Jul 2023 --- Bachelor's Degree.

PROJECTS

IRIS

| Apr 2023 - Jul 2023

A medical chat-bot trained with static textual data.

Link: Iris

KRAKEN

| Oct 2021 - Current

Kraken is an open-source modern math library that comes with a fast-fixedmatrix class and math-related functions.

Link: Kraken

CERTIFICATES

CS50

| Oct 2020 - Oct 2021

CS50 (Computer Science 50) is an on-campus and online introductory course on computer science taught at Harvard University and Yale University

Link: Certificate